centurynovelty.com 2009-12-27

# Century Novelty - Privacy

  * Our Commitment To Privacy 
  * The Information We Collect 
  * How We Use Information 
  * Our Commitment To Data Security 
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy 
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information 
  * How To Contact Us 

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Century Novelty website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address
  * Phone number 
  * Credit/Debit Card Information 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Phone Number 

## How We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We also use cookies to assist in retargeting advertising. We work with FetchBack to display Retargeted ads to our site prospects, on our behalf, across the Internet. They collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected during in this process. To read FetchBack’s Privacy Policy, [click here](http://www.fetchback.com/privacy.html). If you do not want FetchBack to collect this information, you may opt out of their service. Opting out will not in any way effect your use of our site. To Opt-Out, of FetchBack Retargeting, please [click here](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html). Visit the Network Advertising Initiatives Opt- Out by [clicking here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We use the latest technology in online security such as site identification and data encryption. With site identification your browser automatically ensures that you are connected only to our Web site. If a problem arises your browser will alert you to the potential loss of security.

The strict data encryption that we use hides sensitive information like your name, address, and credit card information. Our ordering process is protected by the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, which encrypts your information and confirms the identity of the Century Novelty server before allowing your shopping cart to be checked out. Modern browsers support the SSL protocol. We recommend that you use the latest browsers to ensure that you are protected by advances in security technology.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by calling us at 1-800-325-6232 or sending us an email at [info@centurynovelty.com](mailto:info@centurynovelty.com). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-325-6232 or send us an email at [info@centurynovelty.com](mailto:info@centurynovelty.com).
